Hey, big brother, how long are you going to sleep? It's starting! Yakanta Idol!
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku has an announcement!
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku Spring Tour 2023 100% Erythm will start on April 15th!
There are still tickets available, so please come and see us at the venue near you!
And on May 3rd!
Single movie will be released today! Please check it out too!
Last but not least, Yakan-kun will give you a cup of tea to cheer you up!
Do you usually drink tea?
Oh, I drink green tea every day!
Really?
Yes, I do.
Today's tea is a quick green tea!
Wow!
Wow! Thank you! Bon appétit!
Thank you!
Oh, it's so good! It's so relaxing!
I don't know, it has less bitterness.
It's so easy to drink! It's so good!
Good, good, good!
I'm glad to hear that you've had Yama-chan's!
Now, I'm sorry to leave you with this, but I'm going to end on a cute note!
Yes!
Can I ask you to close for the camera?
Next time, please let us do a comedy like "All hands on deck at 8 o'clock"! Thank you very much, this is Shiritsu Ebisugaku no Katamimi no Naka.
This show is about Toshikazu-chan.
Mon-chan
Mr. Aoi
Mr. Seiji
This program was provided by Mr. Gura.
Thank you very much.